AJIN: DEMI-HUMAN
深く眠れるかい？
傷は癒せたかい？
Do you sleep well?
Did your wounds heal?
Just cos' they say the night is lonely
夜が寂しいからって
無理して
誰かを愛さないで
You don't have to force yourself
To love someone
They say I'm dreaming
夢を見る事だって
咽び泣く事だって
They say I'm sobbing
They say I tried to die without knowing
知りもしないまま
死んでみたって
上手に隠れたかい？
息は潜めたかい？
Did you manage to hide?
Did you hold your breath?
今が苦しいからって
Just cos' they say it's tough now
You don't have to force yourself to change
無理して自分を変えないで
Even a brave savage
勇敢な蛮人だって
悩める子羊だって
Even a troubled lamb
回り道して生きているって
They are just wandering through life
So I don't stand out
目立たないように
So I can put up with it
堪えられるように
So my train of thought won't stop yet
思考回路はまだ
止めないように
Tonight RUN A WAY RUN A WAY
It's unbelievable
今宵 RUN AWAY  RUN A WAY
嘘みたいだ
Someone take my hand
誰かこの手
掴んでくれよ
The tomorrow we can't see
Doesn't have to come
見えない明日は来なくていい
Now I just want to sleep
今はただ 眠りたい
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING? WHY ME...
はっ
うっ
Damn it, why is this happening?
なんで こんなことになったんだ
Why am I...?
なんで僕が…
No, I know why.
いや なんでってそりゃ…
If they catch me,
もし捕まったら きっと
本当に不死身かどうか調べられる
they'll test to see
if I'm really immortal.
AJIN EXPERIMENT
They'll kill me over and over again.
何度も何度も殺される
No. Anything but that! When I...
嫌だ… それだけは嫌だ！
あの時…
（衝突音）
The moment I died...
ほんの一瞬…
いや 一瞬よりは長く…
No, it lasted longer than an instant.
I was in so much pain.
痛かったんだ… すごく！
Really horrible pain.
くそ　なんでこんなことに…
Damn it.
Why is this happening?
Kei.
（海斗）
圭…
えっ？
We're okay.
今は大丈夫だ
We've gone pretty far
on these mountain roads.
山道通って
距離もだいぶとったし―
The police probably can't fully mobilize
so quickly either.
警察もそんなに早く
本気で動けないだろ
And it's not like everybody's watching
the news.
一般人だって みんなが
ニュース見てるわけじゃないしさ
I've got a place in mind where we can wait
for things to settle down.
とりあえず落ち着ける場所
目星は付けてあるんだ
We can think about our next move
when we get there.
そこに着いたら
いろいろ考えればいい
うん
Kai...
カイ その…
うん？
I'm sorry about this morning...
今朝は… ごめん
Don't worry about it.
いいよ 別に
And...
でさ…
do you think...
あの… 僕って
やっぱ 人間じゃないのかな？
I'm really not human?
I don't really care either way.
その辺は興味ねぇわ
（サイレン）
According to police reports,
（キャスター）
警察の発表によりますと―
the Ajin and his accomplice may have
already fled the prefecture.
亜人は協力者と共に―
既に県外へ
脱出している可能性もあり
A full-on search will start at sunrise,
他県警とも連携し―
in cooperation with police
from other prefectures.
日の出と共に
本格的な捜索に入るとのことです
That's all from the Ajin's house.
以上　亜人自宅前からでした
We'll keep you informed
of further developments as we hear them.
続報が入りしだい
また お伝えいたします
And we're out. Good work.
（ディレクター）
はい オッケー　お疲れ
ふう
（車のドアの閉まる音）
あっ
Yes, I've just arrived.
はい　今 到着したところです
問題ありません
It will not be a problem.
Yes.
ええ　やつらに奪われる前に
必ず捕獲します
I assure you, I will have him in custody
before they can get to him.
Who's that...?
（キャスター）
あれは…？
（ディレクター）
うん？
ああ 厚生労働省のお偉いさんだな
A big shot in the Ministry of Health,
Labor and Welfare.
Pretty much the top when it comes
to dealing with Ajins.
まあ 亜人関連の実質的トップだ
The woman may be his secretary.
女の方 秘書かな？
（キャスター）
ふーん　イケメン キャリア
Good looks, good job... He's not bad.
悪くないわね
Yeah, yeah.
（ディレクター）
はいはい…
（荒木(あらき)）
トザキさん お疲れ様です
Good evening, Mr. Tozaki.
We spoke on the phone earlier. I'm...
先ほど電話で
お話しさせていただいた…
-It's Tosaki.
-Huh?
（戸崎）
トサキです
は？
It's Tosaki, not Tozaki.
トザキではなく トサキです
（荒木）
あ… それは 大変失礼しました
Oh, how rude of me.
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）
はぁ…
Just as you advised, we've significantly
increased our manpower.
（荒木）
ご進言いただいたとおり
人員を大幅に増やしました
We're also coordinating
with other police forces.
警視庁や他県警との連携も
抜かりはありません
そうですか
I see.
（荒木）
うわ…
ん…
Oh, no, thank you.
あ いえ　私は結構です
配備した人員の装備は？
How are your deployed personnel equipped?
はあ　装備ですか？
Equipment? Well, they all have
their usual equipment.
装備の方は その… 通常通りの
装備をしておりますが
After all, we have no experience
with Ajins...
何分 亜人に関しては
我々も経験がなく―
If there's some sort of special equipment
that we need--
もし 何らかの特殊な装備が
必要であれば…
これを
I've prepared these myself.
私の方で手配しておきました
うん？
"Non-lethal tranquilizers"?
“非致死性麻酔薬”？
This is the most effective way
to stop an Ajin.
亜人の動きを止めるのに
最も有効な手段です
One hit will bring them down, guaranteed.
当たりさえすれば
確実に仕留められます
With this...
（荒木）
はぁ… こんな物まで…
We expect them to arrive
in about two hours.
２時間ほどで到着の見込みです
Once they do, distribute them
to your forces at the scene right away.
着いたらすぐに
現場各員に配備してください
え… 了解です
Understood.
But...
でも… 麻酔薬とか仕留めるとか
まるで狩りですね…
tranquilizers and "bringing them down,"
it's almost like hunting--
まさに狩りです
It is hunting.
Ajins are a rare organism.
亜人は稀少な生物ですから
The last time I saw him
was this afternoon.
（慧理子）
最後に会ったのは今日の午後です
But I really don't know anything.
でも ホントに何も知りません
Was your brother acting strangely at all?
（刑事）
お兄さんに変な様子とか
なかった？
No, he was the same as always.
別に いつも通りでした
You didn't notice anything at all?
Aren't you his sister?
（刑事）
何も気付かなかったの？
妹さんでしょ？
何を気付けっていうんですか？
What should I have noticed?!
（刑事たち）
ああっ…
You can't tell if someone's an Ajin
until they die, right?
亜人って 死ななきゃ
分からないんですよね？
So, there was nothing to notice.
気付きようがない
まあ そうなんだけど…
Well, true, but...
I don't know...
私は知らない
I don't know anything about my brother.
兄さんのことなんて
何も分からない
（計量機の自動音声）
いらっしゃいませ
エンジンを停止してください
Welcome.
Please turn off your engine.
Why are you helping me, Kai?
（圭）
カイは どうして
助けてくれるんだ？
（海斗）
うん？
If you're with me,
you'll be in danger, too.
僕といれば
カイまで危険にさらされるんだぞ
Well, we're friends, right?
だって 友達だろ？
Even though I'm an Ajin?
（圭）
亜人なのに？
フッ それは関係ねぇだろ
That has nothing to do with it.
So, how many Ajins are there
in the world again?
ていうか 亜人て
世界に何人いんだっけ？
え？
えっと 46…
Forty-six-- No, wait, 47, I guess,
if you include me.
いや… 47人かな　僕も入れて
Oh.
なんだ　47人もいるのか
There are 47 of you?
That's not so rare, then.
大して珍しくもねぇな
フフッ… ありがとう カイ
Thanks, Kai.
I think I feel a little better.
少し気が楽になったかも
That's good.
（海斗）
そりゃよかった
（車の音）
はっ やべっ 出るぞ
Damn, we gotta go.
う… うん
（女子高生）
ううっ… ううっ…
What a lousy time to run out of gas.
（チンピラ）
このタイミングで
ガス欠とか ありえねぇ
（チンピラ）
ちっ あー うっせぇな！
Shut up!
Don't worry, we'll have some fun
before we sell you.
売る前に楽しむからよ
ちっと待ってろ！
（女子高生）
ううっ… ううっ…
あっ
-Hey, that was...
-What?
おい 今の…
あ？
あっ あ…
100 MILLION YEN REWARD
FOR THE AJIN'S CAPTURE
You gotta be kidding me.
マジかよ…
Damn... If we'd caught him, then we could
have gotten a hundred million yen.
（渡辺(わたなべ)）
惜しかったなぁ
あん時 捕まえてたら
１億円もらえてたのに
If we'd known about it beforehand...
（太田(おおた)）
事前に知ってたらねぇ
If only he'd died when we were
the only ones around.
（渡辺）
僕たちだけしかいない時に
死んでくれたら よかったのに
（太田）
アッハ…
So, what are we gonna do
about our Physics homework?
ていうか 物理の課題どうする？
永井君頼みだったのに
We always got it off Nagai.
（渡辺）
あっ それだけは残念だね
Yeah, I guess
that's the worst thing about this.
（笑い声）
あっ… 何？ どうしたの？
What, something wrong?
It's nothing.
（中島(なかじま)）
何でもない
Stop quibbling. Just do your job.
（荒木）
いちいち質問するなよ
いいから動け
But, Mr. Araki...
（警官）
しかし 荒木さん…
あ？　だから お前の意見は
聞いてないって言ってんだろ
Huh? Didn't I just say,
I'm not asking for your opinion?
I guess that's as much as we can expect
from the local police.
警察といっても
所轄のレベルでは あの程度か
What about applying
the Ajin Protection Law?
（泉）
亜人保護法を適用しては？
追跡にはマンパワーが必要だ
The pursuit requires manpower.
We don't want them turning against us.
上から抑えつけて
反発されてはかなわん
-Don't interfere.
-Yes, sir.
余計な口をきくな
はい
（荒木）
あの…
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
お話し中 失礼します
-What is it?
-Well...
何か？
（荒木）
はい あの…
亜人の早期確保のため―
It'd really be helpful to know
a bit more about Ajins
出来れば もう少し
亜人に関する情報を頂けないかと…
in order to capture it
as quickly as possible.
（うめき声）
Hey, what are you doing?
おい 何してんだよ？
Shut up. Just look straight ahead
and drive, jerk.
（チンピラ）
うっせぇな 前見て運転しろ ハゲ
Are you really sure it was the Ajin?
（チンピラ）
つーか ホントに亜人なのかよ？
間違いねぇって
I told you, I'm sure of it.
はぁ…
（圭）
うっ…
Kai.
カイ
（海斗）
うん？
I know it's not a good time, but I...
こんな時に
その… あれなんだけど…
Well, I really have to pee.
すごく おしっこしたい
ああ じゃあ 脇道入ろう
Okay, let's find a side street.
（圭）
はぁ…
So, pee comes out normally.
おしっこは普通に出るんだな…
そりゃそうだ
I guess that makes sense.
I lived a normal life
until today after all.
僕だって今日まで
普通に生活してたんだし…
はっ！
（殴る音）
（チンピラの笑い声）
おっ… ん？
（圭）がっ！
（海斗）あっ！
（圭）あっ ううっ…
（海斗）圭！
Kei?!
はぁっ はぁっ はぁっ…
ううっ うっ…
Well?!
どうだ？
Holy shit, it really is the Ajin!
Holy shit!
間違いねぇ　亜人だ！
マジで亜人だぜ！
Seriously?! I can't believe it?!
A hundred million yen!
マジかよ？　信じらんねぇ
１億だぜ！
We're rich! Holy shit, we're rich!
Oh, my God!
マジでもらえんの？
なあ マジでもらえんのかよ？
やべぇじゃん！
Who the hell are you?!
何だ お前ら！
Where the hell did you come from?!
どっから湧いてきやがった！
うう… ううっ
ああ？　お前こそ何？
亜人の友達？
And who are you? The Ajin's friend?
We'll be keeping this Ajin,
just so you know.
亜人君はもらってくから
よろしくー
Like hell you will!
（海斗）
勝手に話進めてんじゃねぇ！
（女子高生）
はっ… 亜人？　ホントに？
Is it really an Ajin?
あっ…　うっ くっ…
（ガムテープが切れる音）
（女子高生）ううっ
No... No!
（圭）
嫌だ… 嫌だ…！
（チンピラ）
いてっ！
（圭）
がっ！
圭！
Kei!
（殴る音）
ぐっ うっ…
Time to see if you really can't die.
マジで不死身か試してやるよ
Why is this happening?
（圭）
なんで こんなことになったんだ？
なんで…
Why?
I didn't do anything wrong!
僕は悪くないのに！
（チンピラ）
おら！ 不死身なんだろ！
Come on! You can't be killed, right?!
How about it!?
どうなんだよ！
ハハハ… １億もらっちゃうよ
That hundred mil is mine.
死ん… じゃ… え
All of you...
お前ら… 全員…
Just die...
ううっ…
Die...
死ん…
え？　あれ？
死なないんだよな？
Huh? What?
They don't die, right?!
Kei!
圭！
（チンピラ）うりゃあ
（海斗）ああっ
くっ…
Why me...?
（ＩＢＭ）
なんで僕が… なんで…
Why...?
No, never mind that.
なんでって そりゃ…
はぁっ！
（チンピラ）
がっ！
Kei!
（海斗）圭！
（殴る音）
うっ ぐっ…
（うめき声）
（チンピラ）
お おい…
Hey, this Ajin died!
この亜人 死んじまったぞ！
No.
（圭）
違う…
I'm...
僕は…
（叫び声）
What's happening?
何？
あっ うっ…
My body won't move.
（海斗）
体が… 動かねぇ
はぁっ… だぁっ… はぁっ…
It's like when I was leaving school.
（圭）
下校の時と同じだ
So, this is what this does!
これってやっぱり
こういうことなんだ！
（圭）えいっ！
（チンピラ）ああっ
ああっ あ あっ…
Kai, can you stand up?! Let's go!
カイ 立てるか？　逃げよう！
くっ… うっ…
あっ！　はぁっ はぁっ…
This part is well known...
（戸崎）
有名な話ですが―
but beware of an Ajin's voice.
亜人の声には注意してください
Yes, I've heard of that.
ああ… 聞いたことがあります
It's like temporary paralysis
that lasts for a few seconds.
金縛りにあったように
数秒間 動けなくなるとか
人体に影響はありませんが―
It does no physical harm,
but you must take care
when you're trying to capture them.
捕獲の際は
少々気をつけねばなりません
（チンピラ）
あ…
（チンピラたち）
ああ… はぁっ…
You okay?
体 大丈夫か？
Other than getting punched...
殴られた以外はな
くそっ 追うぞ！
Damn it, we gotta go after them!
（チンピラ）あっ！　女がいねぇ
（チンピラ）ほっとけ！
-The girl's gone!
-Forget her!
Hurry up, dumbass!
早くしろ ハゲ！
ああっ… しくったぜ
We screwed up!
A voice that stops people's movement.
人の動きを止める声ですか
不思議なもんですね
That's so strange.
Do you know how they do it?
それって
解明されてるんでしょうか？
I'm not at liberty to say.
研究中につき お答えできません
うーん…
Mr. Araki.
（警官）
荒木さん
ん？　ああ…
Mr. Toza-- Mr. Tosaki.
とざ…
（せきばらい）
戸崎さん
母親への聴取 終わったそうです
It seems they're done questioning
the mother.
（戸崎）
うん… では
Well, then...
ああ その前に
１つ よろしいですか？
May I ask one thing before that?
Yes?
はい？
あの… 亜人に関して
他に何か隠してない… ですよね？
You're not hiding anything
about the Ajins, are you?
アッハハ… あっ いえ あの…
よく言うじゃないですか
No, I mean, you hear it all the time,
right? That they're always hiding stuff--
“上はいろいろ隠してる”って
I won't say
that we're not hiding anything.
隠していることが
ないわけではありませんが―
But there's nothing other than the voice
that will affect any of you.
“声”以外で あなた方に
影響するようなことはありません
Ajins aren't inherently dangerous.
You have my word.
亜人に危険性はない
それは絶対です
Well, then, good luck.
では ご健闘を
Sir.
はっ
We're not human.
我々は人間ではない
When we're on duty, we're something else.
We're public officials.
公務中は公人という
別の生き物なのだ
The more you acknowledge that,
the less sentiment you'll feel.
それを深く認識しておけば
無用な感傷は消せる
Remember that.
覚えておきたまえ
Izumi Shimomura.
下村泉君
（泉）
あっ はい
Yes, sir.
Ajins aren't inherently dangerous.
亜人に危険性はない
As long as Kei Nagai isn't a variant.
永井圭が別種でない限り
うん？
（金属音）
え！？
-What is it?
-Nothing.
（海斗）
どうした？
え？　あ… いや
Kei, I'm sorry, I let my guard down.
I didn't think this would happen.
圭 悪い　油断した
いきなりこんなことになるなんて
Don't worry about that.
But you-- You're injured.
そんなこと… それより ケガ…
あっ！
くそっ！
Damn it.
We got you!
逃がすか くそったれ！
Run them over!
It won't actually kill them!
ぶち当てろ！
死んでも死なねぇんだ！
（チンピラ）ひき殺せ！
（チンピラ）了解！
Got it!
-Are they trying to hit us?!
-They're insane!
（海斗）
ぶつける気か！？
何なんだよ こいつら！
お前らなんかがいるから…
お前らなんか…
It's because of you guys that...
Because of you guys...
Go! Smash them!
いけ！　ぶちかませ！
Damn it.
（チンピラ）ああ…
（チンピラ）くそっ
（遮断機の音）
Kei, we're not stopping!
（海斗）
圭 このまま突っ込むぞ！
ああっ…
Nice!
（海斗）
ツイてる！
ぐっ…
-Go?! We gonna go?!
-Hell yeah!
行く？　行っちゃう？
だよな？
Yeah, we're gonna make it!
Smash on through!
よっしゃ 間に合うぞ
ぶっちぎれ！
（ブレーキ音）
The hell are you doing, dumbass?!
馬鹿野郎 何やってんだよ！
早く出せ！
Hurry and move!
Hey! Don't mess around!
おい！　ざけんな！
う… 動かない…
-Won't move...
-What? The engine stalled?!
はぁ？　エンストか！？
No...
（チンピラ）
違う…
ああっ… ああ…
か… 体…
My body...
ああっ…
I didn't do anything wrong.
（ＩＢＭ）
僕は… 悪くないのに
死んじゃえ お前ら…
全員 死んじゃえ…
Just die.
All... of you... die...
あ… ああ…
（悲鳴）
（衝突音）
（爆発音）
うん？　何だろう？
-What was that?
-Don't know.
（海斗）
さあな…
でも 多分 振り切れた
But I think we lost them.
Back there, why was I the only one
who could move again so soon?
あん時 なんで俺だけ
すぐに動けたんだ？
That made it clear.
（圭）
さっきのでハッキリした
An Ajin's voice can stop people
from moving.
亜人の声には
人の動きを止める作用があるらしい
Maybe...
まだ 何かあるんじゃないか？
there are more things I can do...
...as an Ajin.
亜人てのは…
I really...
（ＩＢＭ）
すごく… おしっこしたい…
have to pee.
TO BE CONTINUED
If my wish would come true
願い叶(かな)うなら
もう一度
Once again
I wanna touch your heart
君の心に
触れていたい
No matter how dark it gets
どんな闇でも
探してるんだ
I'll be searching
For my one
たったひとつの
光を
And only light
As I look up to the stars
Even though you are far
遠いけど
You're looking up at the same starry sky
同じ星空　見上げてる
In the sky of my heart
心の空には
雫(こぼ)れ落ちそうな
It's about to spill over
Your smile and
君の笑顔と
ぬくもり
Your warmth
Hear me
Until I went away and
Faced the lonely days
愛することの意味なんて
I thought I could understand
What it means to love
分かってたつもりだった
Feeling everything that
Was right in front of me
大切なもの失って
Losing something precious
Realizing real love
本当の愛に気付いて
I'll tell you now
I'll tell you now,
Just how close you are